Arun P Lukose

2020

Indian Citizen

Email arunplukose@gmail.com

Website arunplukose.com

Contact +91 9496071920

I'm a **Visual Effects Compositor** from India doing feature film works. Loves the entire process of film making as I've worked as a DOP and Editor for many projects. Keen into programming and math to better build, experience and share the whole process for myself and the community.

Professional Experience

Dec. 2016 - Sept. 2019: DOP, Editor, Colorist - Rubberband Official and freelance

Sept.2018 - Sept.2019: Freelance Compositor - various indie projects

Sept.2019 - Present : Digital Compositor at Digital Turbo Media

Softwares and Skills

The Foundry Nuke:
Adobe Premiere Pro:
Adobe Photoshop:
PFTrack
Mocha
Autodesk Maya:

Programming/scripting skills with Python.

Experience as cinematographer for various short films and music videos.

Showreel

Reel https://vimeo.com/349005260

Education

Bachelor of Technology in Chemical Engineering | 2013 - 2017 Plus Two - Holy Cross HSS, Cherpunkal | 2011 - 2013 SSLC - De Paul HSS Nazareth hill | 2010-2011

Responsibilities Undertaken

Technical event coordinator at college technical fests. Active participant in college Film club. Volunteered at NSS,Oasis Pain & Palliative Care.

Languages

Interests